Guide to the Phyllis Chesler Papers, 1968-2003 RL.00221
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings Series, 1969-1988 and undated
  - About Men subseries, 1970-1979, bulk 1974-1978
    - Typescripts, 1971-1979, bulk 1975-1978
      - Bibliography (Box W20)
      - Bibliography (Box W20)
      - "Talking to Men," "Brothers" (Box W20)
      - Part I: Male Images: Reflections of Eden (3 folders) (Box W20)
      - Preface (2 folders) (Box W20)
      - Material left over for Preface/Epilogue (Box W20)
      - Annotated Bibliography (Box W21)
      - Male Realities (Box W21)
      - Incomplete Preface (Box W21)
      - Preface and 2cc (Box W21)
      - "Relatives" (not usable) (Box W21)
      - Aug. 10, 1976 (Box W21)
      - Autobiographical Portraits (Box W21)
      - "Mothers and Sons," "In New York City" (Box W21)
      - Pages 10 to 280 (Box W21)
      - "Mothers and Sons," "Fathers and Sons" (Box W21)
      - "Phallic Sexuality," "Men in School," "Brothers" (Box W21)
      - Male Realities (2 folders) (Box W21)
      - Part I: Male Images (4 folders) (Box W21)
      - Preface: Original (Box W21)
      - Part II (original) (Box W21)
      - Part II: Male Realities: Autobiographical Portraits: 1961 to 1971 (Box W21)
      - Men Now, Upon Being Interviewed, An Essay (Box W21)
      - Interviews (Box W21)
      - Part Two: Male Realities (Box W21)
      - Pages 14 to 44 (Box W21)
      - Part I (Box W21)
      - Printer's Galleys (Box W21)
      - Preface (Box W21)
      - Lovers and Warriors (Early Version) (2 folders) (Box W21)
      - Lovers and Warriors (Box W22)
      - "Men Now, Upon Being Interviewed" (Box W22)
      - "Brothers," and "Men on Male Violence: The View from Prison" used, July 1976 (Box W22)
      - Part Three: Men Now, Upon Being Interviewed. An Essay, 1975 (Box W22)
      - "Brothers," "Phallic Sexuality," "Male Emotions," "Fathers and Sons," "Talking to Men" used/rewritten, July 23, 1976 (Box W22)
      - Re-Done Originals, June 9, 1976 (Box W22)
      - Part Two: Male Realities: Autobiographical Portraits: 1961 to 1971 (Box W22)
      - Part One: Male Images (Box W22)
      - Section One. Carbons to be Inserted (Box W22)
      - Writing for Male Realities. Used (Box W22)
      - Bibliography (Box W22)
      - Part III Essay Original, 1975 (Box W22)
      - Part Two: Male Realities: Autobiographical Portraits: 1961 to 1971 (Box W22)
      - "Brothers," "Men in New York City," "Men in Iranistan" (Box W22)
      - On Fathers and Sons (Box W22)
      - Annotated Bibliography (Box W22)
      - Pat's Copy of Male Images, Nov. 1, 1976 (Box W22)
      - Entire Book (1 folder) (Box W22)
      - Entire Book (3 folders) (Box W22)
      - Model Copy of Book (3 folders) (Box W22)
      - "An Essay About Men" (Box W23)
      - Epilogue and Annotated Bibliography (Box W23)
      - "Male Realities": Autobiographical Portrait (Box W23)
      - "Fathers and Sons" (Box W23)
      - Entire Book (3 folders) (Box W23)
      - Original Copy (2 folders) (Box W23)
      - "Male-Female Relationships" (Box W23)
      - "Successful Warriors: Money" (Box W23)
      - Myths Held by Men (Box W23)
      - Male-Female Rape (Box W23)
      - Socialization and Childhood (Box W23)
      - Male Images of Women (Box W23)
      - Male Success: Money (Box W23)
      - Male-male Practices (Box W23)
      - Work: Relativism and Feminism (Box W23)
      - About Male Infancy (Box W23)
      - In Revolutionary Times: "Male Psychology" (Box W23)
      - Anti-Feminist Writing (Box W23)
      - Male Psychology Book -- two outlines (Box W23)
      - Fathers and Sons, ca. 1975 (2 folders) (Box W23)
      - Rationale Cum Illustration: Treatment (Box W23)
      - Original II (Box W23)
      - Carbon of Original I (Box W23)
      - Lovers and Warriors: First draft/proposal (Box W23)
      - Layout (proofs of title pages) (Box W23)
      - Outline -- Lovers and Warriors, Conversations with Evil; Pre-working of Book II, Jan. 1975 (Box W23)
      - About Men: A Psycho-Sexual Meditation by Phyllis Chesler, 11/17/77 (bound typescript) (Box W24)
      - About Men: A Psycho-Sexual Meditation by Phyllis Chesler (2 bound typescripts) (Box W24)
      - All About Men (formerly Lovers and Warriors) by Phyllis Chesler, August, 1976 (loose typescript) (Box W24)
      - About Men: A Psycho-Sexual Meditation by Phyllis Chesler, undated (Phyllis' copy) (Box W24)
      - About Men, ca. 1978 (unbound proof) (Box W24)
  - With Child subseries, 1977-1979
    Typescripts of various drafts of the book and two sets of proofs. Original arrangement has been retained. A group of some 50 audiocassettes from the 1970s is arranged at the end of this subseries. Many are untitled and are not necessarily related to With Child. The largest individual segment of these concerns an appearance with Margaret Mead in Cincinnati in 1977.
    - Motherhood Journal, Jan., 1977 to Jan., 1979 (Complete carbon copy I) (2 folders) (Box W25)
    - Journal of Pregnancy and Motherhood, May 15, 1977 to July 20, 1978 (Box W25)
    - 1977 Taxes (Box W25)
    - Proof, Oct. 10, 1978 (Box W25)
    - Edited out material, Nov. 11, 1978 (Box W25)
    - Proof, Dec. 11, 1978 (Box W25)
    - Motherhood Journal, ca. 1978 (Box W25)
    - Proof, Jan. 4, 1979 (Box W25)
    - Author's first proof, May 2, 1979 (2 folders) (Box W25)
    - Proof, May 16, 1979 (2 folders) (Box W25)
    - Advance praise for With Child, undated (Box W25)
    - A Diary of Motherhood, undated (typescript) (3 folders) (Box W25)
    - Journey into Motherhood, undated (typescript) (2 folders) (Box W25)
    - Motherhood: Spirit and Flesh by Carol Christ, undated (Box W25)
    - Photographs, undated (Box W25)
    - Proof, undated (Box W25)
    - With Child: A Diary of Motherhood, 1977 (typescript) (2 folders) (Box W26)
    - With Child: A Diary of Motherhood, 1977 (typescript) (2 folders) (Box W26)
    - Untitled Slides (Box 26)
    - Audiocasettes, 1972-1981, undated
      A group of some 50 audiocassettes from the 1970s and 1981. Many are untitled and are not necessarily related to With Child. The largest individual segment of these concerns an appearance with Margaret Mead in Cincinnati in 1977.
      - D., Jim, May 4,1981 (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - C., Pat, May 19, 1981 (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - T., Walter, Aug. 12, 1981 (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - The male sample -- give up: de Lay, Antrofus, Elkin, Knowlton, Weiss, Hurwit, Helford, Hertz (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - Excerpts: 1) Williams, 2) Comments on Interviews, 3) Silkwood, 4) Gilda J., 5) Ann C., 6) Custody writing -- Chesler, Aug. 31, 1981 (audiocassette) Fleminger, Brinton, Purpura, Green, Rodriguez, Schulman & Kozak (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - The Janeways (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - Chamlin, Trudy, Cranston, Betty Friedan (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - 1) "Working moms," 2) Faery tales, 3) Victim 4) Clytemnestra 5) Travel -- Daghir, 6) Treen and prison, 7) Custody and moving, 8) Hanamaka, Sept. 21, 1981 (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - T., Barbara (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - Helford, Hurwitz, Gilliam, Carbon, Robbins (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - 1) Aristobus -- joint custody, male abandonment, 2) Jennifer F., 3) Bocarda FF (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - Chamlin, Trudy, Cranston, and Betty Friedan (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - Robbins, Roland, diMarco, Gibbons, Wickham, Kippersmith (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - D., Howard (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - W., Lynn: 1) Kids becoming commodity, 2) Father's behavior (ex-criminal) (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - R., Ann (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - R., Ann, June 27, 1981 (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - Phyllis Chesler/Margaret Mead dialogue, Jan 14, 1977 (13 audiocassettes) (Box 26)
      - Chesler/Mead dialogue 1977; Chesler/Laing dialogue, 1972; Marilyn Powell (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - Lois N. April 4, 1981 (2 audiocassettes) (Box 26)
      - Chesler, Phyllis (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - Spafford, Belle and Baker (Gibbs) (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - K., Judge Dorothy and Dr. B. (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - H., Elenore H., Marie S., and Doris T. (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - M., Patsy, et al. (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - S., Saul and Harriet P. (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - Dr. S., Dr. B., and Flo K. (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - C., John H. and Emily Y. (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - A., David (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - A., David (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - M., Patsy (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - Reich (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - S., Anna and Lionel T. (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - R., Roz, Barbara B., et al. (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - Sept. 15, 1976 (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - 1) Jerry H., Aug. 30, 1981, 2) H. Davis, Sept. 1, 1981, 3) Newsclipping -- Maternal Abuse, 4) Grief Critiqued, 5) Lawcase -- no role leeway for women, 6) Medea, 7) Gender Statistics, 8) Working Moms (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - S., Gail, Jane T., and Ana F. (audiocassette) (Box 26)
      - R., Dorothy and Larm R. (audiocassette) (Box 26)
  - Mothers on Trial subseries, ca. 1979-1985 (Box W27)
    Includes the following subseries: Research Files, Transcripts, Audiocassettes, and Chapters.
    - Research Files
      Photocopies of articles, clippings, notes, and copies of court cases about child custody. Arranged in alphabetical order.
      - 1800 to 1816 (Box W27)
      - 1817 to 1836 (Box W27)
      - 1837 to 1842 (Box W27)
      - 1843 to 1853 (Box W27)
      - 1854 to 1864 (Box W27)
      - 1865 to 1879 (Box W27)
      - 1880 to 1899 (Box W27)
      - 1900 to 1943 and General (Box W27)
      - Abandonment by Mother (1981) (Box W27)
      - Abdullah, 1980 (Box W27)
      - Adulterous Moms and Custody (1943 to 1969) (Box W27)
      - Jacqueline A. (Box W27)
      - Anon v. Anon (Box W27)
      - Anon v. Anon (Box W27)
      - Beck v. Beck (Box W27)
      - Beck v. Beck Trial Opinion (Box W27)
      - Bezou v. Gaines (Box W27)
      - Black Mothers (Box W27)
      - Blackburn (Box W27)
      - Blackburn v. Blackburn (Box W27)
      - Blain, Bunim, Grimditch (Box W27)
      - Blain v. Blain (Box W27)
      - A Chariot Will Come, by Susan Flakes w/ Phyllis Chesler (Box W27)
      - Charts and Outline (Box W27)
      - Child Custody Laws -- Gen.; Divorce Laws, Battles -- Gen. (Box W27)
      - Child Support (Sept. 1979) (Box W27)
      - Children: Choosing Cults, Drugs, Runaways (Box W27)
      - Children: Choosing Fathers (Box W27)
      - Coding Schedule (Box W27)
      - Cross-Cultural Comparison (Oct. 1979) (Box W27)
      - Custody (Box W27)
      - Custody (Box W27)
      - Custody: Bezou v. Gaines (Box W27)
      - Custody Experts and Expert Opinions (Box W27)
      - Custody Experts (Interview Master List) (Box W27)
      - Custody Interview (Master List) (Box W27)
      - Custody Interviews (Phone number lists) (Box W27)
      - Custody (Joint) (Box W27)
      - Custody Lost by Mothers to State (Box W27)
      - Custody Won by Father (Box W27)
      - Custody Won by Mother (Feb. 1981) (Box W27)
      - Daghir (2 folders) (Box W27)
      - Daghir v. Daghir (Box W27)
      - Data Sheets (Box W27)
      - H. D., Sheila (Box W27)
      - Decisions -- Bould, Painter v. Bannister (Box W27)
      - Dempsey (Box W27)
      - Dempsey v. Dempsey (Box W27)
      - Divorce (2 folders) (Box W27)
      - Divorce Jewish Style and Anti-Feminist Undertones of a Courtroom by Esther Shapiro (1973) (Box W27)
      - Dog Sheets (Box W27)
      - Dog Sheets (data) (Box W27)
      - Economics (2 folders) (Box W27)
      - Embryo Technology (Box W27)
      - "Estimates of National Child Support Collections..." (1985) (Box W27)
      - Extended Family and Custody (Box W27)
      - Family and Schizophrenia (Box W28)
      - Family's Influence on Deviant and Psychotic Children (Box W28)
      - Fathers and Schizophrenia (Box W28)
      - Fathers (1985) (Box W28)
      - Fetal Policies (1985) (Box W28)
      - Finances (Box W28)
      - Fishman, Tina "Uppity" (Box W28)
      - Foetal Politics: Fritz, 1982 (Box W28)
      - Form Originals (Box W28)
      - FP (1982 to 1983) (Box W28)
      - Gallant v. Gallant (Box W28)
      - Billie Lee G. (Box W28)
      - Garska v. McCoy (Box W28)
      - Going to Court (Box W28)
      - Good State (Box W28)
      - Gould v. Gould, 1983 (Box W28)
      - Gulyas v. Gulyas, 1977 (Box W28)
      - Help Moms Material (1980 to 1984) (Box W28)
      - Homosexuality (Box W28)
      - "Inmate Mothers and Their Children " (1979) (Box W28)
      - International Custody Laws (Box W28)
      - International Responses, Aug. to Sept. 1983 (Box W28)
      - International Chapter Names/Address -- Requests/Thanks (Box W28)
      - "Judges:" Chapter 14 (Box W28)
      - "Judges:" Chapter 14 (Box W28)
      - J., Mary Jeanne (Box W28)
      - Labow, 1982 (Box W28)
      - Lambda Legal Defense & Education Fund, Spring 1981 (Box W28)
      - Last Proposals (Box W28)
      - Law Precedents: Foetal Politics (1980 to 1981) (Box W28)
      - Legal (General) (Box W28)
      - Legal History of Custody (Box W28)
      - Lehr (Box W28)
      - "Lesbian Mothers:" Chapter 7 (Box W28)
      - "Lesbian Mother:" Chapter 7 (2 folders) (Box W28)
      - Library Research (Box W29)
      - Lieberman, Rochelle (Letters, "kidnapping" articles), 1977, 1980 (Box W29)
      - Literary Quotes (Box W29)
      - Louden, 1981 (Box W29)
      - Mack v. Rumsfeld, "The Role of the Father" (Box W29)
      - "Males, Fathers, and Husbands" (1977) (Box W29)
      - Master List (Box W29)
      - Master List: Addresses (Box W29)
      - Master List: Old Interviews (Box W29)
      - Master List: Phone Numbers (Box W29)
      - Master List: Fathers (Box W29)
      - Master List: Fathers' Rights, Activists/Experts (Box W29)
      - Master Files (Box W29)
      - Master List: Interviews (Box W29)
      - McBride v. McBride (6 folders) (Box W29)
      - McBride v. McBride, ca. 1977 to 1978 (Box W29)
      - McBride -- Extra Copies (2 folders) (Box W29)
      - McBride -- Miscellaneous (Box W29)
      - Medea (Box W29)
      - Millovich: Excerpts of Law Decision (Back of Book), 1982 (Box W29)
      - Miscellaneous (1980 to 1981) (Box W29)
      - Miscellaneous Clippings (July 1981) (Box W29)
      - Miscellaneous Clippings (Aug. to Sept. 1981) (2 folders) (Box W29)
      - Miscellaneous Clippings (Nov. to Dec. 1981) (Box W29)
      - Miscellaneous Clippings (1982) (Box W29)
      - Mothers and Schizophrenia (Box W29)
      - "Mothers in Prison": Chapter 17 (Box W29)
      - "Mothers in Prison": Chapter 17 (Box W29)
      - Mothers -- Influence (Box W30)
      - Newspaper Clippings, January 1985 (Box W30)
      - Parental Events (1900 to 1943) (Box W30)
      - Paternal Custody: 1968 to 1984 (1979) (Box W30)
      - "Poor Mother": Chapter 8 (2 folders) (Box W30)
      - Porter v. Porter (Box W30)
      - Psychosis, General (Box W30)
      - Pulitzer v. Pulitzer, 1984 (Box W30)
      - Questions, Dog Sheets, Data Sheets (BLANK) (Box W30)
      - Raw Materials (Box W30)
      - Real/False Names (Box W30)
      - Refugee Children (Box W30)
      - Reimbursement Folder (Box W30)
      - Research for Ch. 1: Pre-hist: 1599 (Box W30)
      - Research for Ch. 1: 1601 to 1800 (Box W30)
      - S., Kersten (Box W30)
      - Schuster v. Schuster, Isaacson v. Isaacson (Box W30)
      - Selective Typing (Box W30)
      - Simmons v. Simmons, 1978 (Box W30)
      - Slavery (Box W30)
      - The State & Custody (General) (Box W30)
      - Summary of Studies (1982) (Box W30)
      - Tapes Out (Box W30)
      - To Be Xeroxed, Miscellaneous (Box W30)
      - Transcript Check-out (Box W30)
      - Typing Schedule (Box W30)
      - W., Arlene Susan, 1983 (Box W30)
      - Witches: "How Witchcraft Trials are Conducted" (Box W30)
      - Women's Forum (1984) (Box W30)
      - Women's Rights (1601 to 1800) (Box W30)
    - Transcripts
      Transcripts of interviews with parents involved in custody cases. Arranged in alphabetical order. These overlap but do not exactly match the Audiocassettes subseries.
      - B., Jill (Box W30)
      - B., Lynn (Box W30)
      - B., Susan (Box W30)
      - B., Pat (Box W30)
      - B., Jo (Box W30)
      - C., Julie (Box W30)
      - D., Hubert m/won (Box W30)
      - D., Gus m/lost (Box W30)
      - E., Mary Beth (Box W30)
      - G., Billie (Box W30)
      - G., Billie P. (Box W30)
      - G., Peter m/won (Box W30)
      - G., Brian m/lost (Box W30)
      - H., Shiela (2 folders) (Box W30)
      - H., Jane (Box W30)
      - H., Steve (Box W31)
      - H., Steve m/lost (Box W31)
      - H., Dr. Robert (Box W31)
      - H., Robert (Box W31)
      - H., Robert m/won (Box W31)
      - H., Phyllis (Box W31)
      - H., Neil (Box W31)
      - H., Mary (Box W31)
      - H., Gerry (lost custody of mother) (Box W31)
      - J., Susan (Box W31)
      - J., Jean, May 19, 1981 (Box W31)
      - K., Ken, m/gave up (Box W31)
      - L., Jean (Box W31)
      - L., Ilke (Box W31)
      - M., Isabelle (Box W31)
      - Medea (Box W31)
      - M., Jan (Box W31)
      - N., Lois (Box W31)
      - R., Douglass (Box W31)
      - R., David (Box W31)
      - S., Judith (Box W31)
      - S., Alan (Box W31)
      - T., Jean (Box W31)
      - V., Bruce (2 folders) (Box W31)
      - X., George (2 folders) (Box W31)
      - W., Maggie (Box W31)
      - W., Henry (Box W31)
      - W., John (2 folders) (Box W31)
      - W., Lillian (Box W31)
      - A to F (Coded Interviews) (Box W31)
      - G to L (Coded Interviews) (Box W31)
      - M to R (Coded Interviews) (Box W31)
      - S to Z (Coded Interviews) (Box W31)
      - Double Standards/Double Binds (need % for groups) (Box W31)
      - Interview Quotes (Discarded) (Box W31)
    - Audiocassettes
      Audiocassettes of interviews about various court cases, filed in alphabetical order. These overlap with but do not exactly match the Transcripts subseries.
      - A., Joan (Women -- Lost custody; transcript original) (Box W31)
      - A., Joan, April 27, 1981 (Women -- Lost custody, transcribed originals) (2 tapes) (Box W31)
      - A., Zahra (Iraq) and F., Eva (Ghana), Jan. 18, 1984 (Box W31)
      - B., Jill, May 5, 1981 (Box W31)
      - Barb/Phyllis -- Book, Feb. 5 (Memos and Notes) (Box W31)
      - B., Mary, April 16, 1981 (Women -- Gave up transcript) (Box W31)
      - B./B., Lynn, March 21, 1982 (Women -- Won custody; transcribed, originals; Lynn B./B. -- W., Kay) (Box W31)
      - B., Susan (Box W31)
      - B., Susan, July 22, 1981 (Box W31)
      - Blank (no title) (Memos and Notes) (Box W31)
      - B., Judith and A., Joan (Women -- Lost), April 30, 1981 (Box W31)
      - Brian, June 19, 1981 (Box W31)
      - B., George, May 1, 1981 (Men -- Lost transcript) (Box W31)
      - Budapest, May 18, 1981 (Memos and Notes) (Box W31)
      - Budapest, May 18, 1981, WHW (Memos and Notes) (Box W31)
      - B., Pat, May 9, 1981 (Box W31)
      - B., Pat, May 9, 1981 (Women -- Lost custody; transcript original) (Box W31)
      - B., (?) Oct. 14, 1980 (Memos and Notes) (Box W31)
      - B., Jo, Aug. 25 and 26, 1981 (Box W31)
      - B., Jo, Aug. 25, 1981 (Box W31)
      - B., Jo, Aug. 26, 1981 (Women -- Lost) (Box W31)
      - C., Julie, Jan. 3, 1981 (Women -- Lost) (2 tapes) (Box W31)
      - C., Paula, April 19, 1981 (2 tapes) (Women -- Lost custody; transcribed, original; Burg -- W., Maggie) (Box W31)
      - Carole, Feb. 2, 1981 (Women -- Lost custody) (Box W31)
      - C., Ilene, (Women -- Lost custody) (Box W31)
      - C., Madeline, July 10, 1981 (Women -- Gave up transcript) (Box W31)
      - C., Margery, "Working as a 'Success' Among Traditional Women," Oct. 26, 1980 (Memos and Notes) (Box W31)
      - C., Margery (Memos and Notes) (Box W31)
      - C., Margery -- WHW, Aug. 3, 1981 (Memos and Notes) (Box W31)
      - C., Carol, Dec. 25, 1980 (Women -- Gave up transcript) (Box W31)
      - C., Don, July 24, 1981 (Men -- Lost transcript) (Box W32)
      - Counseling -- Rape, March 3, 1980 (Memos and Notes) (Box W32)
      - D., Elaine, May 2, 1981 (Women -- Gave up transcript) (Box W32)
      - D., Elaine, May 2, 1981 (Women -- Gave up transcript) (Box W32)
      - D., H., Sept. 8, 1981 (Box W32)
      - D., Charlotte, Aug. 10, 1981 (Experts) (Box W32)
      - D., Rosemary and W., Kay, Feb. 25, 1981 (Women -- Won) (Box W32)
      - D., Gus, Aug. 8, 1981 (Men -- Lost transcript) (Box W32)
      - Donohue, Feb. 5, 1981 (Box W32)
      - D., Susan, May 15, 1981 (Box W32)
      - D., Diana, Feb. 20, 1981 (Women -- Gave up transcript) (Box W32)
      - D., Jephane, Sept. 3, 1981 (Women -- Lost custody) (Box W32)
      - E., Mary Beth, Jan. 8, 1981 (Women -- Lost) (3 tapes) (Box W32)
      - E., Saul -- Gave up, May 28, 1981 (Box W32)
      - Empty case (Memos and Notes) (Box W32)
      - E., Barbara, April 4, 1981 (Box W32)
      - Eunice, Aug. 18, 1981 "Betrayal in Female" (Memos and Notes) (Box W32)
      - F., Susan, Oct. 7, 1980 (Memos and Notes) (Box W32)
      - F., Joseph (Box W32)
      - F., Sue -- WHW, Oct. 7, 1980 (Memos and Notes) (Box W32)
      - F., Irvin, July 19, 1981 (Men -- Lost transcript) (Box W32)
      - F., Doris J. (Untranscribed Experts) (Box W32)
      - G., Aviva, Jan. 4, 1981 (2 tapes) (Box W32)
      - G., Lynn -- won May 19, 1981 (Box W32)
      - G., Billie, Oct. 21. 1981 (Box W32)
      - G., Billie Pirner, April 24, 1982 (2 tapes) (Box W32)
      - G., Margaret, June 15, 1981 (Box W32)
      - G., Pete and W., Henry, Aug. 5, 1981 (Men -- Lost transcript) (Box W32)
      - G., Pete, Aug. 4, 1981 (Men -- Won transcript) (Box W32)
      - G., Belinda, April 2 and 3, 1981 (Box W32)
      - G., Belinda, April 5, 1981 (Box W32)
      - G., Richard and Voeller (Experts) (Box W32)
      - G., Stu, July 22 and 23, 1981 (Men -- Won transcript) (Box W32)
      - G., Jean, May 19, 1981 (Box W32)
      - H., Jen, June 7, 1981 (Men -- Won transcript) (Box W32)
      - H., Jen, Oct. 28, 1981 (Men -- Won transcript) (Box W32)
      - H., Mary, 1980 (Box W32)
      - H., Mary, Dec. 6 (Box W32)
      - H., Mary, Feb. 26 and 27, 1981 (Box W32)
      - H., Mary, Feb. 27 and 28, 1981 (Box W32)
      - H., Ned, Aug. 25 (Men -- Lost transcript) (Box W32)
      - H., Ned, Aug. 25, 1981 (Box W32)
      - H., Sheila, Aug., 1981 (Women -- Lost custody) (Box W32)
      - H., Thelma, (2 tapes) Jan. 26, 1981 (Box W32)
      - H., Jane, June 15, 1981 (Women -- Lost) (Box W32)
      - H., Jane P., June 11, 1981 (Women -- Lost) (Box W32)
      - H., Steve, June 7, 1981 (Men -- Won transcript) (Box W32)
      - H., Robert, Aug. 11, 1981 (Women -- Won custody; transcribed, originals; Lynn B./B. -- W., Kay) (Box W32)
      - H., Robert, Aug. 6, 1981 Transcribed (Men -- Won transcript) (Box W32)
      - H., Ellen and H., Michele, Dec. 8 (Box W32)
      - H., Ellen, Dec. 7, 1980 (Box W32)
      - H., Phyllis, Feb. 21, 1981 (Box W32)
      - H., Pat, April 15, 1981 (Women -- Lost) (Box W32)
      - Interview with Holland Feminists (Memos and Notes) (Box W32)
      - J., Brian, Jan 19, 1981 (Men -- Won transcript) (Box W32)
      - J., Susan, May 21, 1981 (Women -- Lost custody) (Box W32)
      - J., Barbara, Feb. 16, 1981 (Untranscribed Experts) (Box W32)
      - K., Phyllis, (Untranscribed Experts) (Box W32)
      - K., Roberta, Aug. 10, 1981 (Women -- Lost custody) (Box W32)
      - K., Pam, May 20, 1981 (Box W32)
      - K., Pam, May 21, 1981 (Box W32)
      - Knott's Landing, Dec. 9, 1981 (Box W32)
      - K., Lillian and S., Joanne, July 17, 1981 (Experts) (3 tapes) (Box W32)
      - K., Lillian, Aug. 2 (Experts) (Box W32)
      - Kuppersmith on parenting (Experts) (Box W32)
      - L., Jean, April 2, 1981 (Women -- Gave up transcript) (Box W32)
      - Lesbian Mother Defense Fund -- Pam, Joan, Geraldine, May 21, 1981 WHW (Memos and Notes) (Box W32)
      - L., Beverly, July 11, 1981 (2 tapes) (Box W32)